recommendedjobs.com 2017-12-12

# Recommended Jobs | Privacy

#### Updated April 14, 2015

Welcome to RecommendedJobs.com ("Recommended Jobs"). We respect the privacy of our users who access and/or use Recommended Jobs and are committed to protecting the personally identifiable information we collect about you.

By using the Recommended Jobs website, or submitting your information to us by any other means, you are subjecting your information to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact Recommended Jobs at 17602 E. 17th Street Suite#102-280, Tustin, CA 92780 or via our contact form located here.

#### What This Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers how Recommended Jobs collects, uses, and shares your personal information when you visit Recommended Jobs' website and when you use Recommended Jobs services.

Recommended Jobs is not responsible for any practices of third parties that we do not own or control. This includes the collection of your information from websites that we may link to. Please review the privacy policies of those sites so that you may better understand how they collect, use, and share your information.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Recommended Jobs may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any updates on our website located at [www.recommendedjobs.com](http://www.recommendedjobs.com/).

Recommended Jobs encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this site and/or submitting your personally identifiable information to Recommended Jobs will be subject to the then current Privacy Policy.

#### Information That We Collect

Recommended Jobs collects two types of information about you when you use our website and our services. The first type of personal information we collect is anything you actively choose to disclose to Recommended Jobs ("Active Information.") The second type of information is anonymous aggregate information collected in a way that is not visible to you or others visiting the site ("Passive Information.")

#### Active Information

Recommended Jobs may collect or receive Active Information about you when you submit your personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, your username, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, interests, job search history, and any other data included in any submitted profile or search. Recommended Jobs also collects information on the pages you access through our site and any other information you may volunteer, such as survey information, ratings, reviews, questions, and answers.

#### Passive Information

Recommended Jobs may also collect your Passive Information by recording actions taken by you on our site including, but not limited to, clicks, page views, IP address, and search queries. We may store this information in our equipment or the equipment of third party technology providers. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you.

#### How We Use Your Information

Recommended Jobs will only use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

For the purpose of identifying users and delivering relevant content and advertisements, our partner LiveRamp may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser or a unique ID for your mobile device. To opt-out of LiveRamp cookies, please go [here](http://liveramp.com/opt_out/).

#### Email Communications

Recommended Jobs respects your email preferences and will never provide your email address to a third party without your permission, except as may be prescribed elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. If you provide us your email address, Recommended Jobs may email you job alerts, account notifications, news, offers, surveys, promotions, and other communications. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Recommended Jobs may use demographic and/or profile data, including but not limited to search history, to tailor your experience on Recommended Jobs' site, show you content that Recommended Jobs thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. Recommended Jobs, or companies we partner with, may contact you based on your interests such as job postings and career development opportunities.

If you do not want to receive particular types of email messages from Recommended Jobs, follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email message to notify us of your preferences, or click here.

#### Website Administration

We may use other companies as necessary to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Every effort will be made to safeguard your privacy when it may be accessed by other companies, including but not limited to technology providers; however, Recommended Jobs will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

Recommended Jobs may use your IP address to administer our site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you, your location, and to gather broad demographic information. Nothing shall restrict Recommended Jobs from maintaining your data following your termination of your use of Recommended Jobs' site. Recommended Jobs may delete your user data at Recommended Jobs' sole discretion.

#### Children's Privacy

Recommended Jobs' site is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. Recommended Jobs is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities. Recommended Jobs does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor does Recommended Jobs target its services or site to children under the age of 13. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 17 ask and receive permission from their parent or guardian prior to using Recommended Jobs or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

#### Protect Yourself

Recommended Jobs uses automated processes and third party aggregators to collect and present information that has been created by third parties, so we cannot verify the accuracy or legitimacy of all job postings displayed on our site. We strongly encourage you to exercise caution when providing information about yourself to others online, including when you apply for jobs found on Recommended Jobs.

Never provide your social security number, credit card information, bank account details, or unnecessary personal information to a potential employer. Never participate in a financial transaction of any sort with a potential employer. Always be cautious of opportunities that sound too good to be true or require you to act as a financial intermediary, particularly for an overseas person.

#### Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computers hard drive. Recommended Jobs may use cookies to keep track of your session and advertising delivery. Recommended Jobs or our partners may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save a password associated with a user profile. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use third-party cookies to record information (excluding your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on others websites. You can learn more [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You can opt-out of this type of advertising here.

#### Links to Third Party Sites

Recommended Jobs may provide links to external websites. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Recommended Jobs of those external websites. You acknowledge that Recommended Jobs is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Recommended Jobs is not responsible for the content of such external websites. Your use of external websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the external websites.

#### Assignment

If there is a change of control in Recommended Jobs' business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise) or if there is an asset sale, the user information, including personal information, could be sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information handling practices as described in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on the site, and you may opt-out of the use of your existing information in a new manner. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of any successors or assigns of Recommended Jobs or the assets of Recommended Jobs.

#### Conditions of Use

If you decide to use Recommended Jobs' site or services, your use and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### Contact Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:

Recommended Jobs  
17602 E. 17th Street Suite#102-280  
Tustin, CA 92780
